// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "A metallic sphere has a cavity of diameter D at its center.If the sphere is heated,the diameter of the cavity will",
    answer: "Increase",
    options: [
      "Decrease",
      "Increase",
      "Remain unchanged",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which solid will have the weakest intermolecular forces?",
    answer: "Ice",
    options: [
      "Ice",
      "Phosphorus",
      "Naphthalene",
      "Sodium fluoride"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "In how many ways can a team of 11 players be formed out of 25 players, if 6 out of them are always to be included and 5 always to be excluded",
    answer: "2002",
    options: [
      "2020",
      "2002",
      "2008",
      "8002"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of these is not true for adiabatic process ?",
    answer: "dT=0",
    options: [
      "dQ=0",
      "dU+dW=0",
      "dT=0",
      "Molar specific heat is zero"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The tendency of a reaction to take place spontaneously is greatest when the reaction is",
    answer: "Exothermic and randomness increases",
    options: [
      "Exothermic and randomness increases",
      "Endothermic & randomness increases",
      "Exothermic and randomness decreases",
      "Endothermic & randomness decreases"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of these is inertial frame of reference?",
    answer: "A observer in cycle moving with constant velocity",
    options: [
      "A observer in car slowing down",
      "A observer in train speeding up",
      "A observer in car in uniform circular motion",
      "A observer in cycle moving with constant velocity"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "A fair die is tossed repeatedly. A wins if it is 1 or 2 on two consecutive tosses and B wins if it is 3, 4, 5 or 6 on two consecutive tosses. The probability that A wins if the die is tossed indefinitely is",
    answer: "5/21",
    options: [
      "1/3",
      "5/21",
      "1/4 ",
      "2/5"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "For the four successive transition elements (Cr, Mn, Fe and Co), the stability of+2 oxidation state will be there in which of the following order?",
    answer: "Mn > Cr > Fe > Co",
    options: [
      "Fe > Mn > Co > Cr",
      "Cr > Mn > Co > Fe",
      "Mn > Cr > Fe > Co",
      "Co > Mn > Fe > Cr"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Television signals on earth cannot be received at distances greater than 100 km from the transmission station. Thereason behind this is that",
    answer: "The surface of earth is curved like a sphere",
    options: [
      "The receiver antenna is unable to detect the signal at a distance greater than 100 km",
      "The TV programme consists of both audio and video signals",
      "The TV signals are less powerful than radi signals",
      "The surface of earth is curved like a sphere"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "If A = {1, 2, 3, 4, 5} and B = {2, 3, 6, 7} then the number of elements in (A×B)∩(B×A) is",
    answer: "4",
    options: [
      "20",
      "18",
      "6",
      "4"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Which of the following statement is not true about the hexagonal close packing?",
    answer: "In this arrangement, spheres of the fourth layer are exactly aligned with those of the first layer",
    options: [
      "The coordination number is 12",
      "It has 74% packing efficiency",
      "Tetrahedral voids of the second layer are covered by the spheres of the third layer",
      "In this arrangement, spheres of the fourth layer are exactly aligned with those of the first layer"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "A small rod of bismuth is suspended freely between the poles of a strong electromagnet. It is found to arrange itself at right angles to the magnetic field. This observation establishes that bismuth is",
    answer: "Diamagnetic",
    options: [
      "Diamagnetic",
      "Paramagnetic",
      "Fern-magnetic",
      "Antiferro-magnetic"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "If p is any statement, then which of the following is a tautology?",
    answer: "p ∨ (~p)",
    options: [
      "p ∧ f",
      "p ∨ f",
      "p ∨ (~p)",
      "p ∧ t"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Out of the following which has highest dipole moment?",
    answer: "cis-3-hexene",
    options: [
      "2,2-dimethyl propane",
      "trans-2-pentene",
      "cis-3-hexene",
      "2,2,3,3-tetramethyl butane"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "A sheet of aluminium foil of negligible thickness is introduced between the plates of a capacitor. The capacitance of the capacitor",
    answer: "Remains unchanged",
    options: [
      "Decreases",
      "Remains unchanged",
      "Becomes infinite",
      "Increases"
    ]
  },


];